<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1252" standalone="yes"?>
<!DOCTYPE document [
  <!ELEMENT document   (languageid,fields,page*)>
  <!ELEMENT languageid (#PCDATA)>
  <!ELEMENT fields     (Bron,Datum,Pagina)>
  <!ELEMENT Bron (#PCDATA)>
  <!ELEMENT Datum (#PCDATA)>
  <!ELEMENT Pagina (#PCDATA)>
  <!ELEMENT page       (pagenumber,text?,image?)>
  <!ELEMENT pagenumber (#PCDATA)>
  <!ELEMENT text       (#PCDATA)>
  <!ELEMENT image      (#PCDATA)>
  <!ATTLIST image      timestamp CDATA #REQUIRED
                       size      CDATA #REQUIRED>
]>
<document>
<languageid>21</languageid>
<fields>
<Bron>De Groene Amsterdammer</Bron>
<Datum>19300111</Datum>
<Pagina>16</Pagina>
</fields>
<page>
<pagenumber>1</pagenumber>
<text>
A L. U Ai F L b Tb LIST OF BÜOKS
PUBLISHED BY
THE HALCYON PRESS (A. A. M. STOLS)
MAASTRICHT
ENGLISH BOOKS
FRENCH BOOKS
I. JOHN KEATS, ODES. 1927.
Composed in Lutetia roman type (lOpt.) LetterJng by J. van Krimpen
Printed at the Halcyon Press.
125 copies on Van Gelder paper bound in parchment exhausted.

II. WILLIAM BLAKE, THE MARRIA(,'E OF HE A VEN AND HELL.
1928.
Composed in Lutetia roman and italic types (14 pt.) Lettering I&gt;y -T- van
Krimpen. Printed by Messrs Joh. Enschedéen Zonen.
300 copies on Pannekoek paper.
In parchment //. 24.

III. DANTE GABRIËL KOSSETTI, HAND AND SOUL. 3928.
Composed in the roman type designed by Peter Schoeffer of Gernsheim
(1450—1502). Lettering by J. van Krimpen. Printed by Messrs Joh. Ensched
en Zonen.
5 copies on vellunï, bound in morocco-leather exhausted.
25 on Japanese vellum, bound in chagrin-leather exhausted.
300 on Van Gelder paper, bound in linen ;'l. 9.—•

IV. EVEBYMAN. A Morality Play o/ the XVth Century. 1929.
Composed in the type engraved by Henric de Lettersnider (XVth Century
Black letter). Printed by Messrs Joh. Enschedéen Zonen.
300 copies on Van Gelder paper, bound in linen 11. 12.50
bound in morocco-leather by Louis Malcorps 11. 40.

V. SIX HYMNS OF HOMER, the drcek iext jaeinf/ the Enr/Ush tmnsUitwn
by Percy Bysshe Shelley. 1929.
Composed in Antigone Greek and Lutetia Roman types (12 pt) both designed
by J. van Krimpen. Initials by the sam&lt;&gt;. Printed by Messrs Joh. Enschedéen
Zonen.
5 copies on vellum, bound in morocco-leather i'xhuusled.
25 on japanese vellum, bound in chagrin leather exhausted.
400 on Pannekoek paper, bound in linen jl. 10.

VI. JOHN MILTON, SONNET S, both English and Italian. 11)29.
Composed in the italic type engraved by Christoffel van Dyck (l(H)l—1070).
Lettering by J. van Krimpen. Printed by Messrs Joh. Enschedéen Zonen.
5 copies on vellum, bound in chagrin leather c-xhnu 'ted. 4
25 copies on japanese vellum, bound in chagrin leather jl.
30.-300 copies on Pannekoek paper, bound in linen il. 10.

VII. JOHN KEATS, SONNETS. 1930.
With a portrait and 10 woodcuts by Jolin Buckla.nd Wright.
Composed in Romanée-type (16 pt), designed by J. van Krimpen. Printed by
Messrs Joh. Enschedéen Zonen.
l copy on pearl-white japanese vellum, contaiiiing the original drawings, the
artist's proofs, and 3 sets of supplemcnta.ry loose proofs of the portrait, the
10 illustrations and 5 rejected woodcuts, signed by the artist (bound in
chagrin leather) jl. l200.
10 copies on pearl-white japanese vellum, containing 3 sets of
supplementary loose proofs of the portrait, the 10 illustrations and 5 rejected wood

cuts, signed by the artist (bound in chagrin leather) il. 200.
25 copies on japanese vellum, containing a supplementary set of loose proofs
of the portrait and the 10 illustrations (bound in chagrin leather) 11. 75.-
300 copies on Pannekoek Halcyon paper, bound in lirieri 11. 25.

VIII. EDGAR ALLEN POE. THE F ALL OF THE HO r S E OF USIIER.
1930.
With 10 aquatints by Alexandre Alexeïeff.
Composed in a roman type engraved by J. M. Fleischrnann (1739). Printed
by Messrs Joh. Enschedéen Zonen.
7 copies on antique japanese vellum containing 3 supplement ary sets of
the engravings (bound in cliagriii leather) jl. 120.
25 copies on japanese vellum, conlaining a supplement ai v set o t' the en

gravings (bound in chagrin leather) 11. 75.
300 copies on Pannekoek paper, bound in linen II. 25.

IN P REP AR AT] ON

T. STURGE MOORK. .\I.\~K l'OKMS. (First Editiom.
EPGAR ALLKX POK. TALKS.
With woodcuts by John ISiickland Wriglil.
PAUL MORAxn'. THE LIVI.\(S nu in ui A.
With 15 aquatints in e.olours l&gt;y Ale\;mdre Aiexeïeff.
WILLIAM KHAKESPEAHE. Til i: T I-J M /'/&gt;"/'.
With woodcuts by .luim Uue.klnnd \V,iul-,l.
THE COMPLFTK WOHKS OF SlIAKKsPi
A new Folio-Kdit ion in one volume.
JOHN KEATS. LETTE/f S TO I-'A\.\}' /-'/,
Edited by J. F. Otten.
I. RAIXER MARIA RILKE, LES ROS ES. 1927.
With a preface TayPaul Valéry.
Composed in a roman type engraved by J. M. Fleisehmann (1739).
LetterinLby J. van Krimpen. Printed by Messrs Joh. Enschedéen Zonen. (First Edition .
20 copies on antique japanese vellum exhnwtled.
250 copies on Van Gelder paper r.xhamtti'd.

II. AXDRE GIDE. LE VOYAOE D'URIEN. 192*.
With woodcut decorations in two colours by Alfred Latour. Composed in Lu

tetia type (16 pt.). Ixittering by Alphonse Stols. Printed at the Halcyon Press.
20 copies on japanese vellum exhaunteit.
250 copies on Pannekoek paper 11. 40.-

III. FRAXCOYS VILLON, OEUVRES COMPLËTES. 1929.
Composed in a XVth Century Black letter. letter-Ing by J. van Krimpen.
Printed by Messrs Joh. Enschedéen Zonen.
15 copies on pearl-white japanese vellum t'yhimnlfii.
105 copies on Pannekoek paper, bound in half parchment f l. 50.

IN PREPARATION

ANDRÉGIÜE, LA SYMPHON1E PASTORALE.
Composed in Romanée type, designed by J. van Krimpen.
ARTHUR RIMBAUD, OEUVRES COMPLETEN.
(Jompos(;d in Monotype-Garamond, hand-set.
CHARLKS irOKLEANS, OEUVRES COMPL1ÏTES.
RUTEBEUF. OEUVRES COMPLETE*.
GERMAN BOOKS
1. GEOKG BÜCHXER, J)A\TO\'S TOD. 1930.
Lettering by A. A. M. Stols. Printed at the Halcyon IV.-s.
Composed in Monotype (iaramond, hand-set.
20(1 copies on Pannekoek a.ntique paper.
In linen
In chagriu-leathei'
In parchment
IN PREPARATION
GOETIIE, WKST-ÖSTLICHER Dl VAX. 1930.
Composed in Erasmus-type designed by S. H. de Kun.-. Initials by the
Portrait engraved on copper by Th. Levigne. Printed at the Haleymi
100 copies on Pannekoek Halcyon paper.
SOPIIOCLKS. AXTICOXE. the Greek text iV:in- the (ierman trans
by Hölderlin.
Composed in Antigone Greek and Lutetia. roman type both designc
J. van Krimpen.
IC. TH. A. HOFFMAXN. DAS MA.1ORAT.
With woodcuts by \V. J. Rozendaal.


GREEK BOOKS

L cf. EXCLISH BOOKS no. V.

H. OMHPOY BATI'AXOMVOMAXIA. 1929.
Composed in Antigone-t ype designed by .1. van Krimpen. Printed hy ,1
.loh. Enschedéen Zonen.
100 eopies on Pannekoek paper, bound in chagrin-leathei- ;,'.

IN PREPARATION
SOP1IOCLKS. Aidinm,,-.


DUTCH BOOKS

L P. ''. ROl'TKNS. (Jf)E\ /-.'.V /•'/.'. H/J//-.' .V TE X I',l A' .v, l l'l'n \, •;•&lt;
voorafgcga-m dooi' diens O D l'] 1.1.V SAPI'O. I92S.
('oni])osed in Luie) ia, roman and ilalie types ihiDt1-. Printed l&gt;v Mi'.-.-r
lMisched(' en Zonen. 1^5 e.,])ie- .,n Pannekeek iiapi :.
In pa,])ei' cover.-, •'/.
In parchment /.'.

TL A. K01.AM) HOLST. III-'.T i:i, l'.s7X&lt;'// l /;///,. i \i, !•'.\ •_,
d.ior !&gt;!•: ZI-:I-:T(&gt;CHT \'.\.\ i!it\.\. zoo.x \'.\.x FKP&gt;\L. m-js.
C	posed in i.ulelia l &gt; pe l Ui pii. L&lt; 'i 11' i- i 11 g l&gt;\ .!. \;:'i Kr:ij|..-,i. P-il
t l i" l la Ie \, in Pri-,-. 2 (i, l c. .pie-. i •;: a'M i'M ie \'a'; &lt; ."ld, i '.-Mier.
I M pa pe:'-; ei )\ , ! -•
i n p;'.'vi'.iai-iu •'..
l': ; • f i a'.;' i i; i • l e • i' t.. t •
IN PREPARATION

</text>
<image timestamp="2002:09:20:20:19:56.00" size="145780">000007SY.TIF</image>
</page>
</document>
